PSU performance have been very good for
the last one year both fundamentally as
well as stockwise right having said that
for the banks uh PSU banks are largely
uh largely deposit lead and liquid Banks
uh we are now going to the environment
where we are expecting liquidity
otherwise to pick up so perhaps time to
look at stocks which has suff suffered
due to lower liquidity uh that said I
think the PSU banks have done a good job
they Contin good job but stockwise I
think we get Delta into the stocks which
has suffered with the liquidity and and
now the liquidity situation getting
better they will benefit from it okay uh
which is the sector to completely avoid
for people tuning in right now if
they're trying to understand because we
are reaching out to viewers not just
with ideas to invest in India but also
as an attempt to educate investors about
the Indian market right so which are the
sectors that you must definitely avoid
if you're looking if you're studying the
Indian market see that way it's very
difficult to term one sector completely
avoid but I can share with you that
where we think the valuations are way
too high not just the companies are the
companies are doing what they're doing
but the expectation bu the valuations
are very high for buy and large the
industrial sector now government capex
at 3 and a half% of GDP has peaked I'm
not seen it come down but the industrial
sector trading at PR how you explain
Industrials in India capital goods most
capital goods companies I think these
companies which are particularly
delivered to government spending I think
they will do well but I think their
valuation at 30 40 time times there's
been massive reating right and given
government spending kind of picking out
I think the elevated expectations of the
markets might not be met in those
segments and for the first time was
getting into India you think index funds
or index ETFs is the best way to play it
because just on the index I left India
in 2019 when the index the Nifty was at
10,000 today it's at 25,000 it's 1 and a
half times higher so how do they play
the Indian markets for foreign investors
individual investors looking into India
sure no we would say suggest that Indian
market there is still lot of
inefficiencies so actively managed fund
I think most of the activ managed funds
they will do better than the market in
fact uh I think uh that is can be said
across the market cap criteria Al large
cap mid cap small cap or flexi Cap all
kind of manag T to with the market so I
think active management is the way to go
in Indian markets